indiablooms.com 2010-11-23

# Portal on Indian News | Indian News Portal | Indian News Online | Latest Indian News |Current Indian News | News From India

Indiablooms ([www.indiablooms.com](http://www.indiablooms.com/)) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

When you register with [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/), we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with www.indiablooms.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

[**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) cookie information and the page you requested. 

In addition, when you use [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/)'s services, you may make some of your personal information public. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return and [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) will not be responsible for the use or misuse of such information. 

[**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services promoted by [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) or other companies, and to contact you about specials and new products. [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) is not responsible for the accuracy, completeness, veracity and reliability of any advertising and content, products and services which may be accessed or advertised to you and [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) will not be liable for any loss or damage arising out of the same. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

[**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.   
[**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:   
We have your consent to share the information;   
We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;   
We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer;   
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or   
We find that your actions on our web sites violate the www.indiablooms.com Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Cookies**

[**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) may set and access www.indiablooms.com cookies on your computer and you may not be able to disable these cookies. [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) ensures that all information collected and accessed by [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) through the access of these cookies will be maintained in accordance with this Privacy Policy.   
[**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/)'s cookies.   
Your [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.   
In certain areas [**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

[**www.indiablooms.com**](http://www.indiablooms.com/) may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions write to us on [**info@indiablooms.com**](mailto:info@indiablooms.com).
